Fred Crawford Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 6. Lowell Thomas Papers Research File, 6; Boxes: 52 - 169
  - Tall Story Club, 1931 - 1936 (Folder 1, Box 152)
  - Tall Story Plagarism, 1935 (Folder 2, Box 152)
  - Tallest Man, 1947 (Folder 3, Box 152)
  - Talley, 1942 (Folder 4, Box 152)
  - Tappin (10th Mtn), 1942 - 1957 (Folder 5, Box 152)
  - Tau Kappa Alpha, 1935 - 1959 (Folder 6, Box 152)
  - Taxes, 1938 - 1960 (Folder 7, Box 152)
  - Taxi, 1931 (Folder 8, Box 152)
  - Taylor, Chas K., 1943 - 1952 (Folder 9, Box 152)
  - Taylor, Clif (Shortees), 1960 - 1965 (Folder 10, Box 152)
  - Taylor, H. P. (Prof.), 1938 (Folder 11, Box 152)
  - Taylor, Henry, 1953? (Folder 12, Box 152)
  - Taylor, Hugh, 1970 (Folder 13, Box 152)
  - Tee - Van, Dr. John, 1967 (Folder 14, Box 152)
  - Teigan, Martin J., 1934 - 1937 (Folder 15, Box 152)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence], 1928 - 1956 (Folder 16, Box 152)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence], 1957 - 1969 (Folder 17, Box 152)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence], 1970 - 1981 (Folder 18, Box 152)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] - Allenby, 1925 - 1965 (Folder 19, Box 152)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] American Tour, 1919, 1969 (Folder 1, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] Arrow, 1962 (Folder 2, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] Autographes, 1940 (Folder 3, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] BBC, 1962 - 1963 (Folder 4, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] Beaumont, 1975 - 1981 (Folder 5, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] Boys, 1938 - 1975 (Folder 6, Box 153)
  - Double Day Picnic, 1935 (Folder 7, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] Emery, 1940 (Folder 8, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] - Film Attempts, 1935 - 1942 (Folder 9, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] Film (1962), 1959 - 1981 (Folder 10, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] - London, Australia, Etc., 1919 - 1922 (Folder 11, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] & LT [Lowell Thomas] Sources [1], undated (Folder 12, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] & LT [Lowell Thomas] Sources [2], undated (Folder 13, Box 153)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on 7P Editions, 1975 (Folder 14, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] - LT [Lowell Thomas] on TEL [T. E. Lawrence] Legend, 1966 (Folder 15, Box 153)
  - LT [Lowell Thomas] on What Might Have Done for TEL [T. E. Lawrence], 1968 (Folder 16, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] Mack, 1970 - 1977 (Folder 17, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] O'Brien, 1964 (Folder 18, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] - Phiby, 1955 (Folder 19, Box 153)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] Queries (Berton), 1934 - 1948 (Folder 20, Box 153)
  - Ratel, 1950 - 1978 (Folder 1, Box 154)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] (7 P Show) Hanson, 1968 - 1970 (Folder 2, Box 154)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] Talk Summary, 1933 (Folder 3, Box 154)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] - TELbHF, 1936 (Folder 4, Box 154)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] by F [?] draft, 1936 (Folder 5, Box 154)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] - WLIA, 1924 - 1971 (Folder 6, Box 154)
  - Telegrams, 1934 (Folder 7, Box 154)
  - TEL [T. E. Lawrence] - Script & Shot List, 1922 (Folder 8, Box 154)
  - Telegraph Regs [Regulations], 1933 (Folder 9, Box 154)
  - Tenbrinck, 1978 - 1979 (Folder 10, Box 154)
  - 10th Anniversary, 1940 (Folder 11, Box 154)
  - 10th Ann [ Anniversary] List of Subs, First Test, Headaches, etc, 1940 (Folder 12, Box 154)
  - 10th Mtn [Mountain], 1941 - 1976 (Folder 13, Box 154)
  - Terris, 1954 - 1964 (Folder 14, Box 154)
  - Tery, David, 1939 - 1961 (Folder 15, Box 154)
  - Thacker, Earl, 1944 - 1971 (Folder 16, Box 154)
  - Thanksgiving, 1939 - 1940 (Folder 17, Box 154)
  - Thayer, Sylvanus, 1960 (Folder 18, Box 154)
  - These Men Shall Never Die, 1943 - 1952 (Folder 19, Box 154)
  - These Men Sequel, 1944 (Folder 20, Box 154)
  - This is Your Life, 1959 - 1981 (Folder 1, Box 155)
  - This Week, 1940 - 1963 (Folder 2, Box 155)
  - Thoma, Melba (Luckner), 1981 (Folder 3, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Anne B., 1955 - 1978 (Folder 4, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Annie, 1968 (Folder 5, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Bertram, 1938 - 1950 (Folder 6, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Carl, 1952 - 1980 (Folder 7, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Carroll D., 1949 (Folder 8, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Charles, 1940 - 1947 (Folder 9, Box 155)
  - Thomas, David, 1974 (Folder 10, Box 155)
  - Thomas, David R., 1908 - ? (Folder 11, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Harriet Wagner, 1869 - 1972 (Folder 12, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Harry A. (Anti - S [Antisonetism]), 1937 - 1981 (Folder 13, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Harry G. Obit. [obituary], 1952 (Folder 14, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Jess, 1933 - ? (Folder 15, Box 155)
  - Thomas, John Charles, 1939 (Folder 16, Box 155)
  - Thomas, John & Reva, undated (Folder 17, Box 155)
  - Thomas, K. F., 1939 - 1966 (Folder 18, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Marrianna K. Munn, 1967 - 1982 (Folder 19, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Mariana - Tax Stuff, 1974 - 1978 (Folder 20, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1936 - 1938 (Folder 21, Box 155)
  - Thomas, R. F., 1954 - 1970 (Folder 22, Box 155)
  - Aunt Rose and Ira F. Thomas, 1931 - 1960 (Folder 23, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Tay, 1957 - 1979 (Folder 24, Box 155)
  - Thomas, Tay - Portrait, 1963 (Folder 25, Box 155)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1940 - 1942 (Folder 26, Box 155)
  - Thompson, Rae, 1935 - 1964 (Folder 27, Box 155)
  - Thornburg, Max (Part I), 1942 - 1967 (Folder 28, Box 155)
  - Thornburg, Max (Part 2), 1942 - 1967 (Folder 29, Box 155)
  - Thornburg, Max - Dissertation, 1982 (Folder 1, Box 156)
  - Thornburg, Pherbia Thomas (Part 1), 1907 - 1980 (Folder 2, Box 156)
  - Thornburg, Pherbia Thomas (Part 2), 1907 - 1980 (Folder 3, Box 156)
  - Thornburg, Pherbia Thomas - Orbit, 1980 (Folder 4, Box 156)
  - Thornburg, Raymond, 1944 - 1981 (Folder 5, Box 156)
  - Thorpe, Jim, 1939 - 1941 (Folder 6, Box 156)
  - 1947 Throat (Jan) (Folder 7, Box 156)
  - Thurber, James, 1949 (Folder 8, Box 156)
  - Tibet (Part1), 1938 - 1939, 1949 - 1950, undated (Folder 9, Box 156)
  - Tibet (Part 2), 1950 - 1956, 1958 - 1959, 1979, undated (Folder 10, Box 156)
  - Tibet (part 3), 1959 - 1966, 1979, 1972, 1975, 1978 - 1979, 1981, undated (Folder 11, Box 156)
  - Speeches LT [Lowell Thomas] Edited, 1976 (Folder 12, Box 156)
  - Tibet, 1977 (Folder 13, Box 156)
  - Tibet Accident, 1949 - 1951, 1965, 1976 - 1978, undated (Folder 14, Box 156)
  - Tibet - America, 1954 (Folder 1, Box 157)
  - Tibet Articles, 1949 - 1950 (Folder 2, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Aufshnaiter, 1950, 1954, 1956 (Folder 3, Box 157)
  - Tibet Bible, 1949 (Folder 4, Box 157)
  - Tibet Broadcasts, 1949 - 1951 (Folder 5, Box 157)
  - Tibet broadcasts, 1969 (Folder 6, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Cantwell, 1965, 1969, 1971, 1974 (Folder 7, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Cats, 1958 (Folder 8, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Critic, 1960 (Folder 9, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Critic (Crosby), 1949, 1960 (Folder 10, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Cortisone, 1950, 1965 (Folder 11, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Cultural Center, 1966, 1968, 1970 - 1979 (Folder 12, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Dalai Lama and LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.], 1979 (Folder 13, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Dalai Lama - Tour, 1966 (Folder 14, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Dogs, 1959, 1960, 1973, 1979 (Folder 15, Box 157)
  - Tibetans Et Al [1 of 2], 1951 - 1981 (Folder 16, Box 157)
  - Tibetans Et Al [2 of 2], 1951 - 1981 (Folder 17, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Fox, 1950 - 1957, 1959, 1964, undated (Folder 18, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Frauds (White Lama), 1949 - 1950 (Folder 19, Box 157)
  - Tibet Fund, 1952 (Folder 20, Box 157)
  - Tibet Game, 1957, 1959, undated (Folder 21, Box 157)
  - Tibet Invasion (Bob Ford), 1949 - 1951, 1957, 1960, 1976, 1978, 1980, undated (Folder 22, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Invasion (Bob Ford), 1957 (Folder 23, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Letter, 1950, 1976 (Folder 24, Box 157)
  - Tibet - Norbli, 1967 - 1970, 1976 (Folder 25, Box 157)
  - Out of this World, 1950 - 1954, 1956 - 1957, 1981, undated (Folder 1, Box 158)
  - Tibet - Out of this World (Film), 1954, 1958 (Folder 2, Box 158)
  - Tibet - PAL, 1950, 1964, 1974, 1976 - 1977, 1980 - 1981 (Folder 3, Box 158)
  - Tibet Preliminaries, 1949 (Folder 4, Box 158)
  - Tibet Queries (Cortisone, be equip), 1950 (Folder 5, Box 158)
  - Tibet Records, 1950 - 1951, 1954 (Folder 6, Box 158)
  - Tibet - Tibetan Relief - Ike [1 of 3], undated (Folder 7, Box 158)
  - Tibet - Tibetan Relief - Ike [2 of 3], undated (Folder 8, Box 158)
  - Tibet - Tibetan Relief - Ike [3 of 3], undated (Folder 9, Box 158)
  - Tibet - " Requests ", 1976 - 1977 (Folder 10, Box 158)
  - Tibet - Revolt, 1959 (Folder 11, Box 158)
  - Tibet - Roberts, 1949 (Folder 12, Box 158)
  - Tibet Scrapbooks (Labeled) SB1 - SB5, undated (Folder 13, Box 158)
  - Tibet - Silent War in Tibet, 1959 (Folder 14, Box 158)
  - Tibet - Skit (1951 - 1953), undated (Folder 1, Box 159)
  - Tibet - Stamp, 1949 (Folder 2, Box 159)
  - Tibet - Subs, 1949 (Folder 3, Box 159)
  - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] Tibet Talks, 1950 - 1952, undated (Folder 4, Box 159)
  - Tibet - LTJ [Lowell Thomas Jr.] talks (Todd), undated (Folder 5, Box 159)
  - Tibet - Tenki, 1950 - 1953, 1955 - 1956, 1958, undated (Folder 6, Box 159)
  - Tibet Third - Eye Hoax, 1957 - 1959 (Folder 7, Box 159)
  - Tibet - Tolstoy, Ilia, 1950 - 1977 (Folder 8, Box 159)
  - Tibet - Tsarong, 1950 - 1981 (Folder 9, Box 159)
  - Tibet - Voice of America, 1950 (Folder 10, Box 159)
  - Tibet - White Lama Portrait, 1952 (Folder 11, Box 159)
  - Tibet - Yale Library, 1957 (Folder 12, Box 159)
  - Timberwolves, 1952 - 1981 (Folder 13, Box 159)
  - Time, 1934 - 1974 (Folder 14, Box 159)
  - Time Capsules, 1965 - 1968 (Folder 15, Box 159)
  - Time Tube, 1939 (Folder 16, Box 159)
  - Tinney, 1939 - 1980 (Folder 17, Box 159)
  - Toastmaster, 1934 - 1952 (Folder 18, Box 159)
  - Tobacco, 1934 - 1960 (Folder 19, Box 159)
  - Todd, Hobart, 1958? (Folder 20, Box 159)
  - Todd, Mike, 1951 - 1972 (Folder 21, Box 159)
  - Toledo, 1930? (Folder 22, Box 159)
  - Tomlinson, 1933 - 1943 (Folder 23, Box 159)
  - Tour Invitations, 1967 - 1973 (Folder 24, Box 159)
  - Townsend, Peter (DTC), 1965 - 1981 (Folder 25, Box 159)
  - Trail of '98 [1998], 1962 (Folder 26, Box 159)
  - Train Botch, 1956 (Folder 27, Box 159)
  - Train Whistle, 1948 (Folder 28, Box 159)
  - Trammell, Niles, 1973 (Folder 29, Box 159)
  - Travel, 1946 (Folder 30, Box 159)
  - Travel - (Africa & H. Richards), 1965 (Folder 31, Box 159)
  - Travel - Antarctica & Around World, 1960 - 1963 (Folder 32, Box 159)
  - Travel Article (FRT), 1924 (Folder 33, Box 159)
  - Travel - 80th Year, 1971 (Folder 34, Box 159)
  - Travel Hall of Fame, 1973 (Folder 35, Box 159)
  - Travel Ideas, 1935 (Folder 36, Box 159)
  - Travel Schedules, ETC, 1957 - 1981 (Folder 1, Box 160)
  - Assorted Travel Scripts, 1958 - 1959 (Folder 2, Box 160)
  - Travel Tapes (Auto), 1965 (Folder 3, Box 160)
  - Travelogues, 1924 (Folder 4, Box 160)
  - Travelogues (& Will Rogers), 1927 (Folder 5, Box 160)
  - Travelogues (Misc), 1936, 1971 (Folder 6, Box 160)
  - Trinity Pawling, 1939 - 1971 (Folder 7, Box 160)
  - Trip, 1971 (Folder 8, Box 160)
  - Trip to NY [New York] with Bobby & Betty, 1935 (Folder 9, Box 160)
  - Trohan, 1970 (Folder 10, Box 160)
  - Trudeau, 1969 (Folder 11, Box 160)
  - Trujillo, 1938 (Folder 12, Box 160)
  - Truman, 1951 - 1965 (Folder 13, Box 160)
  - Tse, K. K., 1974 - 1978 (Folder 14, Box 160)
  - Tucker, Preston, 1949 (Folder 15, Box 160)
  - Tulips, 1939 - 1942 (Folder 16, Box 160)
  - Tunney, 1938 - 1971 (Folder 17, Box 160)
  - TV [television], 1931 - 1981 (Folder 18, Box 160)
  - TV [ television], 1952 (Folder 19, Box 160)
  - TV [television] Ideas/Proposal, 1951 - 1981 (Folder 1, Box 161)
  - TV [television] and Radio Appearances, 1946 - 1981 (Folder 2, Box 161)
  - TV [television] Set, 1954 (Folder 3, Box 161)
  - Twain, Mark - Banquet, 1965 (Folder 4, Box 161)
  - " Twelfth " [Annual] CBS Radio [Affiliates Association Convention], 1965 (Folder 5, Box 161)
  - 20th Anniversary [of on-air appearance], 1950 (Folder 6, Box 161)
  - Twitchell, 1937 - 1959 (Folder 7, Box 161)
  - Twombly, 1950 - 1974 (Folder 8, Box 161)
  - Tynan, 1975 - 1978 (Folder 9, Box 161)
  - U Thant, 1971 (Folder 10, Box 161)
  - U.F.O., 1968 (Folder 11, Box 161)
  - Umscheid, 1947 (Folder 12, Box 161)
  - Unesco, 1946 - 1978 (Folder 13, Box 161)
  - Union, 1933 - 1967 (Folder 14, Box 161)
  - United Airlines, 1959 (Folder 15, Box 161)
  - United Cerebral Palsy, 1957 - 1958 (Folder 16, Box 161)
  - United Nations HQ [Headquarters], 1945 (Folder 17, Box 161)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1944 (Folder 18, Box 161)
  - United Press, 1947 - 1976 (Folder 19, Box 161)
  - Unknown Soldier, 1936 (Folder 20, Box 161)
  - Untermeyer (Bush), 1977 - 1981 (Folder 21, Box 161)
  - Untold Story of Exploration, 1934 - 1936 (Folder 22, Box 161)
  - Unusual/Oddity, 1959 - 1978 (Folder 23, Box 161)
  - Urbahn, 1968 - 1981 (Folder 24, Box 161)
  - U.S. Steel, 1960 - 1961 (Folder 25, Box 161)
  - Utica/NBC Flap, 1932 - 1939 (Folder 1, Box 162)
  - Valens, " Red ", 1948 (Folder 2, Box 162)
  - Valley Vagabonds, 1941 (Folder 3, Box 162)
  - Valparasio, 1910 - 1981 (Folder 4, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Alpha Epsilon [Fraternity], 1923 - 1953 (Folder 5, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Bennett, 1927 - 1953 (Folder 6, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio], Burtis, undated (Folder 7, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Chamness, 1959 - 1968 (Folder 8, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Corboy, 1943 (Folder 9, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Estner, 1959 - 1978 (Folder 10, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Jeannetee (Barnes), 1968 - 1973 (Folder 11, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Koby, 1947 (Folder 12, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Marie (Timmons), 1969 (Folder 13, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Mead, Harry H., 1948 - 1969 (Folder 14, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] Name, 1931 (Folder 15, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Reddie, 1940? (Folder 16, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Stiles, 1944 (Folder 17, Box 162)
  - Valpo [Valparasio] - Vilian, 1939 - 1972 (Folder 18, Box 162)
  - Van, Billy, 1946 - 1971 (Folder 19, Box 162)
  - Van Buren, Abigail, 1979 (Folder 20, Box 162)
  - Van Hessen, Paula, 1967 (Folder 21, Box 162)
  - Variety Salute LT [Lowell Thomas] & Cin's [Cinerama's] 20th, 1973 (Folder 22, Box 162)
  - Veasey, 1940 (Folder 23, Box 162)
  - Venezuela Film, 1937 - 1939 (Folder 24, Box 162)
  - Vester, 1935 - 1978 (Folder 25, Box 162)
  - Vester - Dr. Baney, 1952 (Folder 1, Box 163)
  - Vester - Costello, 1952 - 1953 (Folder 2, Box 163)
  - Vester - Flowers of the Holy Land, 1958 - 1964 (Folder 3, Box 163)
  - BSV [Bertha Spafford Vester] Tours, 1948 - 1950 (Folder 4, Box 163)
  - Vester - Murrow, 1956 (Folder 5, Box 163)
  - Vester - Stinchfield [?], 1956 (Folder 6, Box 163)
  - Vester - Support by LT [Lowell Thomas], 1948 - 1959 (Folder 7, Box 163)
  - Vester - WWI [World War I], undated (Folder 8, Box 163)
  - Vets of Future Wars, 1936 (Folder 9, Box 163)
  - Victor, 1905 - 1980 (Folder 10, Box 163)
  - Victor H.S. [High School], 1906 - 1968 (Folder 11, Box 163)
  - Victor Record, 1915 - 1977 (Folder 12, Box 163)
  - Victor - Carl Thomas, 1952 - 1959 (Folder 13, Box 163)
  - Victor - Denny, 1953 - 1972 (Folder 14, Box 163)
  - Victory - Dray, 1953 - 1964 (Folder 15, Box 163)
  - Eddy, 1933 - 1976 (Folder 16, Box 163)
  - Victor McCombs, Electra, 1961 - 1976 (Folder 17, Box 163)
  - Victor - Fluoride, 1951 (Folder 18, Box 163)
  - Victor - Huff, 1965 - 1970 (Folder 19, Box 163)
  - Victor - Kennedy, 1977 (Folder 20, Box 163)
  - Victor - Latimer, 1968 - 1970 (Folder 21, Box 163)
  - Oliver/Lamb/Roe, Gertrude, 1940 - 1979 (Folder 22, Box 163)
  - Victor - Wilson, 1943 - 1959 (Folder 23, Box 163)
  - Victor Museum, 1961 - 1976 (Folder 1, Box 164)
  - Victory is Our Business, 1943 (Folder 2, Box 164)
  - Viereck, 1937 (Folder 3, Box 164)
  - Vietnam, 1964 - 1968 (Folder 4, Box 164)
  - Vietnam - Perot, 1970 (Folder 5, Box 164)
  - View Master (Sawyer's INC), 1962 - 1974 (Folder 6, Box 164)
  - Villiers, 1948 - 1974 (Folder 7, Box 164)
  - Vinacke, 1914 - 1977 (Folder 8, Box 164)
  - Vine, George, 1956 - 1969 (Folder 9, Box 164)
  - Vine, Selena, 1965 - 1966 (Folder 10, Box 164)
  - Vital Spark, 1948 - 1970 (Folder 11, Box 164)
  - V.M.I. Flap, 1966 (Folder 12, Box 164)
  - Voice of America, 1947 - 1961 (Folder 13, Box 164)
  - Von Braun, Werner, 1962 - 1965 (Folder 14, Box 164)
  - Von Hellens, Paula, 1966 - 1967 (Folder 15, Box 164)
  - Von Hesse, Elisabeth, 1948 - 1964? (Folder 16, Box 164)
  - Von Sax, Wilhelm (WM. Sax), 1914 (Folder 17, Box 164)
  - Von Trapp, 1944? (Folder 18, Box 164)
  - Von Zell, Harry L., 1973 (Folder 19, Box 164)
  - Voorhees, Frederick D. " Skip ", 1969 - 1980 (Folder 20, Box 164)
  - Voorhees, Dr. Irving, 1935 - 1956 (Folder 21, Box 164)
  - Voorhees, Sherman, 1931 (Folder 22, Box 164)
  - Vox Pop, 1943 (Folder 23, Box 164)
  - WAC Reject, 1943 May 2 (Folder 24, Box 164)
  - Wake Up America, 1940 (Folder 25, Box 164)
  - Waldorf, 1933 - 1981 (Folder 26, Box 164)
  - Waldron, Webb, 1919 - 1935 (Folder 27, Box 164)
  - Wallace, Dewitt, 1932 - 1981 (Folder 28, Box 164)
  - Wallace, Geo, 1971 (Folder 29, Box 164)
  - Wallace, Henry A., 1954 - 1962 (Folder 30, Box 164)
  - Wallington, Jimmy, 1933 - 1976 (Folder 31, Box 164)
  - Walters, Barbara, 1975 (Folder 32, Box 164)
  - Waney, Arjun, 1958 - 1959 (Folder 33, Box 164)
  - Wangeman, Frank, 1966 - 1981 (Folder 34, Box 164)
  - Wards, 1931 - 1981 (Folder 35, Box 164)
  - Warrick, 1938 - 1973 (Folder 36, Box 164)
  - Warrick Horses, 1940 (Folder 37, Box 164)
  - Wasburn, Brad, 1934 - 1975 (Folder 38, Box 164)
  - Washington Dinner, 1944 April (Folder 39, Box 164)
  - Watson, Arthur " Dick ", 1954 - 1963 (Folder 40, Box 164)
  - Watson, Thomas J. Jr., 1956 - 1981 (Folder 1, Box 165)
  - Watson - EXC [Explorers' Club] & FRT [Francis Ryan Thomas] Health, 1951 (Folder 2, Box 165)
  - Watson Jr. Marist Summary, 1989 - 1990 (Folder 3, Box 165)
  - Watson, Thos. [Thomas] J. Sr., 1940 - 1954 (Folder 4, Box 165)
  - WCCO [Radio], 1966 (Folder 5, Box 165)
  - We the People, 1940 (Folder 6, Box 165)
  - Weaver, Pat, circa 1960 (Folder 7, Box 165)
  - Webb, Paul, 1940 - 1979 (Folder 8, Box 165)
  - Webster, Opera, 1940 (Folder 9, Box 165)
  - Wedemeyer, 1961 - 1976 (Folder 10, Box 165)
  - Weigel, Dorothy M., 1969 - 1978 (Folder 11, Box 165)
  - Weimer, Charles, 1948 (Folder 12, Box 165)
  - Weiss, Samuel A., 1947 (Folder 13, Box 165)
  - Weller, George, 1974 - 1980 (Folder 14, Box 165)
  - Wells, Carveth, 1932 - 1957 (Folder 15, Box 165)
  - Wendel Flap, 1938 (Folder 16, Box 165)
  - Wessells Flap, 1938 - 1941 (Folder 17, Box 165)
  - West, Paul, 1934 - 1938 (Folder 18, Box 165)
  - West Point, 1976 (Folder 19, Box 165)
  - Western Schedule, 1953 (Folder 20, Box 165)
  - Western Union, 1933 - 1941 (Folder 21, Box 165)
  - Wet/Dry Contro [wet Vs. Dry Controversy], 1946 (Folder 22, Box 165)
  - Where Were You?, 1979 (Folder 23, Box 165)
  - Whipple, Jimmy, 1937 - 1941 (Folder 24, Box 165)
  - Whitehead, Arthur, 1963 (Folder 25, Box 165)
  - Whitewater House, 1931 - 1959 (Folder 26, Box 165)
  - " Whitney ", circa 1930 (Folder 27, Box 165)
  - Who's Who, 1975 (Folder 28, Box 165)
  - Wickes, 1928 - 1975 (Folder 29, Box 165)
  - Wein, Noel, 1962 - 1974 (Folder 30, Box 165)
  - Wilcox, Herbert, 1966 (Folder 31, Box 165)
  - Wilhelm (Sweden), 1927 - 1939 (Folder 32, Box 165)
  - Wilkins, 1931 - 1979 (Folder 33, Box 165)
  - Wilkins Book, 1959 - 1969 (Folder 34, Box 165)
  - Willard (D.C.), 1933 - 1942 (Folder 35, Box 165)
  - Williams, Valentine, 1937 (Folder 36, Box 165)
  - Willkie, W. Endell, 1940 - 1978? (Folder 37, Box 165)
  - Wilson, Frank (Film dist [ digest]), 1932 - 1943 (Folder 38, Box 165)
  - Wilson, Jim, 1933 - 1937 (Folder 39, Box 165)
  - Wilson, Walter (Milton, PA), 1933 - 1953 (Folder 40, Box 165)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 1917 - 1978 (Folder 1, Box 166)
  - Winchell, Walter, 1935 - 1975 (Folder 2, Box 166)
  - Windhover (Waller), 1980 - 1981 (Folder 3, Box 166)
  - Windsors, 1941 - 1972 (Folder 4, Box 166)
  - Wings Over Asia, 1935 - 1943 (Folder 5, Box 166)
  - Winslow, Walter G. " Windy ", 1972 (Folder 6, Box 166)
  - Winslow, Win Beverly C - R, 1938 (Folder 7, Box 166)
  - Winston, circa 1946 (Folder 8, Box 166)
  - Winter Carnival, 1940 (Folder 9, Box 166)
  - With Alenby [In the Holy Land] (book), 1936 - 1970 (Folder 10, Box 166)
  - Withrow, Pat B., 1936 - 1955 (Folder 11, Box 166)
  - Witoga Oil, 1936 - 1942 (Folder 12, Box 166)
  - WJR, 1948 (Folder 13, Box 166)
  - Wolfal, Mac, 1944 - 1980 (Folder 14, Box 166)
  - Wolper, David, 1967 (Folder 15, Box 166)
  - Woman's Press Club of NYC, undated (Folder 16, Box 166)
  - Women, 1942 - 1973 (Folder 17, Box 166)
  - Wodfill, 1931 - 1980 (Folder 18, Box 166)
  - Woodfill Reviews, 1930 (Folder 19, Box 166)
  - Woodington, 1950 (Folder 20, Box 166)
  - Wolcott, Alexander, 1937 (Folder 21, Box 166)
  - Woolrich Hall of Fame, 1980 (Folder 22, Box 166)
  - Wooten St. George's Society of NY, 1958 (Folder 23, Box 166)
  - Worcester - Uranium, 1952 - 1953 (Folder 24, Box 166)
  - World Book, 1960 (Folder 25, Box 166)
  - World Letters, 1938 - 1939 (Folder 26, Box 166)
  - World of Lowell Thomas (BBC), 1965 - 1978 (Folder 27, Box 166)
  - World Series, 1939 - 1961 (Folder 28, Box 166)
  - World War I, 1919 - 1948 (Folder 29, Box 166)
  - World War II, 1939 - 1941 (Folder 30, Box 166)
  - World War II, 1941 - 1972 (Folder 1, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Article, 1941 (Folder 2, Box 167)
  - World War II - Asia, 1945 - 1978 (Folder 3, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Asia Diary, 1945 May (Folder 4, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Baseball, 1942 (Folder 5, Box 167)
  - World War II - Canada, 1939 - 1942 (Folder 6, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] - Dogs, 1944 (Folder 7, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] - Europe, 1947 - 1971 (Folder 8, Box 167)
  - [World War I] Europe Broadcasts, 1945 April - May (Folder 9, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Eur [Europe] Diary, 1945 April (Folder 10, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Finnish Relief, 1939 - 1940 (Folder 11, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Greek Relief, 1941 (Folder 12, Box 167)
  - World War II MSS, 1935? - 1944 (Folder 13, Box 167)
  - (War) Name, 1942 (Folder 14, Box 167)
  - (War) News Accuracy, 1943 (Folder 15, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Coverage (War) News, 1944 (Folder 16, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Overseas Schedule & Costs, 1945 (Folder 17, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Prophecies, 1942 - 1944 (Folder 18, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] South Am [America], 1943 - 1965 (Folder 19, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Ski, 1943 (Folder 20, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Travel Plans, 1941 - 1943 (Folder 21, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] " War on " Train, 1943 (Folder 22, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] War Stunts, 1942 - 1945 (Folder 23, Box 167)
  - WWII [World War II] Women, 1943 (Folder 24, Box 167)
  - Wartime Speaking/Work, 1942 - 1945 (Folder 25, Box 167)
  - Wartime Speaking/Work [originally 1 file], 1942 - 1945 (Folder 1, Box 168)
  - Wartime Speaking/Work [originally 1 file], 1942 - 1945 (Folder 2, Box 168)
  - World's Fairs, 1937 - 1964 (Folder 3, Box 168)
  - World's Work, 1935 - 1939 (Folder 4, Box 168)
  - Wouk, 1941 - 1980 (Folder 5, Box 168)
  - WPA [Works Progress Administration] & Flap, 1936 - 1939 (Folder 6, Box 168)
  - Wreck of the Dumaru, 1930 - 1976 (Folder 7, Box 168)
  - Wrench, Sir E., 1934 - 1976 (Folder 8, Box 168)
  - Writing Advice, 1956 (Folder 9, Box 168)
  - Writing Machine [1 of 4] [originally 1 file], 1931 - 1981 (Folder 10, Box 168)
  - Writing Machine [2 of 4] [originally 1 file], 1931 - 1981 (Folder 11, Box 168)
  - Writing Machine [3 of 4] [originally 1 file], 1931 - 1981 (Folder 12, Box 168)
  - Writing Machine [4 of 4] [originally 1 file], 1931 - 1981 (Folder 13, Box 168)
  - Writing Machine, 1931 - 1981 (Folder 14, Box 168)
  - Wylie, Mel, 1940 (Folder 15, Box 168)
  - Wylie, Philip, 1966 (Folder 16, Box 168)
  - Yale, William, 1941 - 1965 (Folder 17, Box 168)
  - Yankee, 1940 - 1960 (Folder 18, Box 168)
  - Yeager, 1948 (Folder 19, Box 168)